luxuryportfolio.com 2007-12-22

# Privacy Policy | Luxury Portfolio

Leading Real Estate Companies of the World (referred to herein as "the Partnership," "we" or "us" or "our") is committed to protecting the privacy of the users of this Website.

This statement discloses our privacy practices. The purpose of this statement is to inform you:

  * What kinds of information we collect from users of the Luxury Portfolio website at (the website) and how such information is collected;
  * How the information is used by us;
  * Whether we disclose any user information to third parties;
  * How you can access, update or delete any information that we collect about you; and
  * The security procedures which we use to protect your personal information.

By using the Website, you signify your assent to this Privacy Policy. We reserve the right to change, modify, add, or remove portions of our Privacy Policy at any time. If so, any such changes will be posted on this page. Please check this page periodically for changes. Your continued use of this Website following the posting of changes to this Privacy Policy will mean you accept those changes.

**HOW WE COLLECT INFORMATION**  
Generally, you can visit the Website without revealing any personal information. Like many Websites, our Web servers collect the Internet Protocol addresses, but not the e-mail addresses, of visitors. This information can measure the number of visits, average time spent on the site, pages viewed, and other such statistics.

In addition, in order for us, our third party content suppliers, or licensees to provide certain services to you, you may be asked for information that identifies you, including your name, e-mail address, mailing address, zip code, telephone number, fax (collectively, "Personal Information"). You may also elect to provide such information to us by sending or responding to e-mails regarding certain listings or services offered on our Website, our third party content suppliers, or licensees. The Partnership, as a customer service, offers links to other sites, and does not assume any responsibility for those sites or their privacy policies and provides those links solely for convenience of the Partnership's visitors. If you link to any other sites, you must do so at your own risk and may rely only on their terms and conditions and privacy policies.

**HOW WE USE AND DISCLOSE YOUR INFORMATION**  
We collect, generate, retain and use your Personal Information for our own internal purposes in connection with the facilitation, recording and processing of any requests, communications, or interactions you may have with our Website. We also collect and store statistics and other information about you and your online activities on an aggregated, non-personally identifiable basis and in a manner that may allow us or our affiliated or related entities, third party content suppliers, or licensees to improve services to you.

In addition, your Personal Information may be also be used by us to provide you with information regarding our products and services. For example, we may use your e-mail address to send you special announcements and notifications of new real estate listings, services or promotions that may be of interest to you.

**COOKIES**  
Cookies are small pieces of information that are stored by your browser on your computer's hard drive. Cookies allow Websites to recognize you when you return and can keep track of information specific to you.

We use a programming tool that uses a temporary cookie to save persistent information on a per session basis. These temporary cookies are discarded as soon as you close your browser. This is a common way of saving persistent data in a Web application. We do not presently use cookies, temporary or permanent, to track users across multiple visits.

In addition, consistent with standard practices in the Internet industry, you may occasionally receive cookies from third parties to which you link from our Website. We do not control these third party cookies, and they are not subject to this Privacy Policy. If you prefer, you may set your browser to ask for your permission before your receive a cookie.

**INFORMATION SHARING AND DISCLOSURE**  
Information about our customers is important to our business, and we are not in the business of selling it to others. We share customer information only with our related or affiliated entities.

**DATA SECURITY**  
Data security is critical to us and thus all Personal Information is held in a secured database. While it is impossible to guarantee the complete security of any computer system and the data contained therein, we maintain and implement robust security policies and procedures that combine with available technologies in accordance with prevailing industry standards, all of which are designed to protect the confidentiality, integrity, and availability of your Personal Information.
